<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" standalone = "yes" ?>
<menulist>
    <menu restaurant="Max & Louie's New York Diner">
        <breakfast hours="all day">
            <item>
                <name>The Standard</name>
                <price>7.95</price>
                <description>
                    Two (2) eggs any-style, home fries, bacon or sausage
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Hash n’ Eggs</name>
                <price>9.95</price>
                <description>
                    Our famous hash made with corned beef, pastrami, potatoes, peppers and onions. Topped with two (2) eggs your way
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Cheesy Omelet</name>
                <price>8.95</price>
                <description>
                    Omelet filled with your choice of American, Swiss, Cheddar or Mozzarella cheese
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>L.E.O. Scramble</name>
                <price>13.95</price>
                <description>
                    Scramble of Nova Lox (smoked salmon), Eggs and Onions
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Salami and Eggs</name>
                <price>11.95</price>
                <description>
                    Grilled Hebrew National salami scrambled with three (3) eggs
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Chili Cheese Omelet</name>
                <price>11.95</price>
                <description>
                    Omelet filled with meat and bean chili, green onions and cheddar cheese
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Build Your Omelet</name>
                <price>11.95</price>
                <description>
                    Choose any three (3) items: spinach, tomato, onions, green peppers, mushrooms, avocado, bacon, ham, sausage, feta, cheddar, American or Swiss
                </description>
            </item>
        </breakfast>

        <lunch hours="all day">
            <item>
                <name>Reuben</name>
                <price>14.95</price>
                <description>
                    Hot pastrami, corned beef, or turkey w/sauerkraut, swiss cheese and thousand island on rye
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Rachel</name>
                <price>14.95</price>
                <description>
                    Hot pastrami, corned beef, or turkey w/cole slaw, swiss cheese and thousand island on rye
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>All Natural Turkey</name>
                <price>10.95</price>
                <description>
                    Turkey Breast with lettuce and tomato on delicious rye bread
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Roast Beef</name>
                <price>10.95</price>
                <description>
                        Freshly sliced roast beef with lettuce and tomato on delicious rye bread
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Turkey Club Sandwich</name>
                <price>12.95</price>
                <description>
                    Turkey breast, swiss cheese, bacon, lettuce, hellman’s and tomato on triple decker rye toast
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Triple Decker Roast Beef</name>
                <price>12.95</price>
                <description>
                    Roast Beef, swiss cheese, bacon, lettuce, hellmann’s and tomato on triple decker rye toast
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Chopped Liver Sandwich</name>
                <price>11.95</price>
                <description>
                    Housemade chopped liver served on rye with lettuce, tomato and red onion
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Kosher Salami</name>
                <price>11.95</price>
                <description>
                    Hebrew National kosher salami on rye bread
                </description>
            </item>
        </lunch>
        <dinner>
        </dinner>
    </menu>

    <menu restaurant="Magnolia Pancake Haus">
        <breakfast>
            <item>
                <name>Magnolia’s Old World Buttermilk Pancakes</name>
                <price>6.99</price>
                <description>
                    Made with Fresh Buttermilk in Small Batches
                </descriptio>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Blueberry Pancakes</name>
                <price>7.95</price>    
                <description>
                    Our World’s Best Buttermilk Pancakes with Wild Blueberries
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Chocolate Chip Pancakes</name>
                <price>7.95</price>
                <description>
                    Semi-Sweet Chocolate Chips Stud Our World’s Best Pancakes
                </description>
            </item>

           <item>
                <name>Apple Cinnamon Pancakes</name>
                <price>8.75</price>
                <description>
                    Granny Smith Apples Scented with Zesty Cinnamon and Cooked Into Our Famous Cakes
                </description>
           </item>

            <item>
                <name>Buckwheat Cakes</name>
                <price>8.50</price>
                <description>
                    Hearty & Healthy Cakes Made with Organic Buckwheat Flour. Treat Yourself Right!
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Silver Dollar Cakes</name>
                <price>6.95</price>
                <description>
                    $10 Worth of The Cutest Cakes You’ve Ever Tasted
                </description>
            </item>

            <item>
                <name>Pecan Pancakes</name>
                <price>7.95</price>
                <description>
                Texas Pecans Fill Our World’s Best Pancakes
                </description>
            </item>
        </breakfast>
        <lunch>
        

    Fried Chicken Chop Salad
    $10.25
    Wedge of Baby Iceberg, Bacon Lardons, Grape Tomatoes, Cucumbers, Fried Egg Ribbons, Crispy Fried Buttermilk Chicken Breast, Haus Smoked Jalapeno Ranch


    Magnolia Cobb

    Organic Mixed Greens, Tomatoes, Gorgonzola Crumbles, Bacon, Hard Boiled Egg, Avocado, Tortilla Strips, Haus Cilantro Ranch Dressing

    $8.49

    Add Grilled Chicken $3.49

    Strawberry Chicken

    Organic Mixed Greens, Gorgonzola Crumbles, Fresh Strawberries, Walnuts, Roasted Chicken Breast, Raspberry Poppy Seed Dressing

    $10.25

    Haus Style Caesar

    Romaine and Arugula, Red Onions, Parmesan Cheese, Haus Baked Croutons, Classic Caesar Dressing

    $6.99

    Add Grilled Chicken $3.49

Haus Burgers
1/3 Lb Brisket Blend Patty and Served with Haus Chips or Audrey's German Potato Salad
Add Soup of The Day for Only $1.99 | Sub Haus Salad for Side $1.99

    Classic Cheese

    Your Choice of Cheese. Served on A Grilled Potato Bun with Lettuce, Tomato and Onion

    $9.99

    Magnolia Patty Melt

    Mixed Grilled Onions & Peppers, Swiss Cheese. Served on Grilled Rye

    $10.25

    Bacon Avocado

    Applewood Smoked Bacon Bits, Tillamook Cheddar, & Avocado. Served on A Grilled Potato Bun with Lettuce, Tomato and Onion

    $11.25

    Breakfast Meets Lunch

    Tillamook Cheddar, Applewood Smoked Bacon, Arugula, Haus Sausage Gravy, Sunny Side up Egg. Served on A Grilled Potato Bun

    $11.99


        </lunch>
        <dinner>
        </dinner>
    </menu>
</menulist>

            <name></name>
            <price></price>
            <description>
            </description>